

# LINDSEY RUGG

Customer Service Representative

## CONTACT



904.624.2911



LindseyWRugg@gmail.com

# **SKILLS**

Analytical thinking, planning.

Accuracy and attention to details.

Organization and prioritization skills.

Problem analysis, use of judgment and ability to solve problems efficiently.

## **EDUCATION**

Utah State University Logan, UT 2012 - 2013

Florida Southern College Lakeland, FL 2008 - 2009

Osceola High School Kissimmee, FL 2008 Graduate

# **AWARDS**

Star of Excellence Internet Sales Award//2013 Centruylink

Outstanding Customer Service//2015 Cruise America

### **PROFILE**

Experienced customer service professional with a background including data entry, sales, multi-line phone skills, and computer proficiency. Able to multi-task and use critical thinking to resolve complex billing issues. Reliable and responsible, working independently or on a team.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Office Skills

- Superior telephone, customer service, and computer skills with proficiency in MS Word, Excel, and Powerpoint.
- Experience with managing money and essential math skills.
- Excellent organizational competence and filing skills.

#### Communication Skills

- Positive, friendly demeanor.
- Able to meet customer needs and exceed set sales goals by providing good customer care and utilizing selling techniques.
- Experienced with appointment setting and callbacks.

#### Management Skills

- Excellent time management skills to quickly and efficiently complete tasks.
- Experienced with inventory management and stocking capability.
- Designed and implemented training program for new employees.

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cruise America // March 2015 - Present Reservation Specialist // Mesa, AZ

D.R. Horton// July 2014 – Jan 2015
Design Administrative Assistant // Jacksonville, FL

Watkins Printing // Jan 2014 – June 2014 Store Associate // Logan, UT

Centurylink // Feb 2013 – Sept 2013 Customer Service Representative // North Logan, UT